var questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which array method removes an element from the end of the array?",
    option1: ".push()",
    option2: ".pop()",
    option3: ".shift()",
    option4: ".unshift()",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which array method removes an element from the begining of the array?",
    option1: ".push()",
    option2: ".pop()",
    option3: ".shift()",
    option4: ".unshift()",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which array method adds an element to the begining of the array?",
    option1: ".push()",
    option2: ".pop()",
    option3: ".shift()",
    option4: ".unshift()",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which array method adds an element to the end of the array?",
    option1: ".push()",
    option2: ".pop()",
    option3: ".shift()",
    option4: ".unshift()",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which array method creates a copy of the results of calling a provided function on every element in the original array?",
    option1: ".forEach()",
    option2: ".sort()",
    option3: ".reduce()",
    option4: ".map()",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which array method  executes a callback function on each element of the array, resulting in a single output value?",
    option1: ".forEach()",
    option2: ".sort()",
    option3: ".reduce()",
    option4: ".map()",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which array method reorders the elements of the array according to the code from the callback function you provide?",
    option1: ".forEach()",
    option2: ".sort()",
    option3: ".reduce()",
    option4: ".map()",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following array methods is non-destructive?",
    option1: ".forEach()",
    option2: ".push()",
    option3: ".splice()",
    option4: ".sort()",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following array methods is destructive?",
    option1: ".map()",
    option2: ".reduce()",
    option3: ".pop()",
    option4: ".slice()",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which array method returns a copy of a portion of an array based on the arguments you pass in?",
    option1: ".map()",
    option2: ".slice()",
    option3: ".reduce()",
    option4: ".unshift()",
    answer: 2,
  },
];

